Finding Aid for the Abiko Family Papers, ca. 1890-1944 LSC.1690
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Incoming Family Correspondence to Abiko Yonako
  - Suto Yae, 1896-1923; 293 Letters & 5 Postcards
    - 8 Letters. (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - (August 5, [1914]).., Postscript. (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - (August 17, [1914]). (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - (August 24, [1914]). (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - (September 8, [1914]). (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - (September 21, [1914])., Enclosure, letter from Yae, (September 22, [1914]). (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - 9 Letters. (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - (October 8, [1914])., 2 Letters. (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - (October 18, [1914]). (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Postscript., (October 24, [1914]) (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - (November 6, [1914]). (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - (November 26, [1914])., Enclosure, List of Presents. (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - (December 3, [1914]). (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - (December 12, [1914]). (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - (December 25, [1914]). (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 8 Undatable Letters, ca. 1911-1913. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - 6 Undatable Letters, ca. 1911-1913. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - 8 Letters. (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - [January 8, 1915]., Enclosed in letter from Tsuda Umeko. (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - (January 15, [1915]). (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - (January 21, [1915]). (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - (January 25, [1915])., Postscript. (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - (January 28, [1915]). (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - (February 8, [1915]). (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - (February 16, [1915]). (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - (February 17, [1915]). (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - 8 Letters. (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - (March 11, [1915])., 2 Letters. (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - (March 19, [1915]). (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - (April 15, [1915]). (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - (May 21, [1915]). (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - (June 4, [1915]). (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - (June 11, [1915]). (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - (June 24, [1915]). (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - 7 Letters. (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - (July 7, [1915])., Postscript. (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - (July 23, [1915]). (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - (July 30, [1915]). (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - (August 12, [1915]). (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - (August 15, [1915]). (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - (August 20, [1915])., Postscript. (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - (September 8, [1915]). (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - 8 Letters. (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - (September 27, [1915]). (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - (October 8, [1915]). (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - (October 20, [1915])., Enclosure, Postcard. (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - (November 4, [1915]). (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - (December 6, [1915]). (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - (December 10, [1915])., 2 Letters. (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - (December 24, [1915]). (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - 8 Letters. (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - (January 16, [1916]). (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - (February 3, [1916]). (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - (March 14, [1916]). (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - (May 15, 1916). (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - (November 24, [1916]). (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - (January 21, [1917])., Enclosures, 2 Joshi Eigaku Juku Alumni Association Notices. (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - (April 8, [1917])., Postscript. (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - (April 27, [1917]). (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - 5 Undatable Letters, ca. 1914-1915. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - 4 Undatable Letters, ca. 1915-1917. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - 5 Letters. (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - (April 2, [1918])., Postscript. (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - (May 5, 6, [1918])., Postscript, Enclosures,2 photographs. (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - (May 16, [1918]). (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - (May 23, [1918]). (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - (September 12, [1918]). (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - 8 Letters. (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - (July 7, [1919]). (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - (August 2, [1919]). (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - (August 14, [1919]). (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - (September 25, [1919]). (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - (October 10, [1919]). (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - (November 7, [1919]). (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - (November 23, [1919]). (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - (November 29, [1919])., Postscript. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - 8 Letters. (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - (January 1, 1920). (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - (February 1, [1920]). (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - (February 12, [1920]). (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - (March 4, [1920]). (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - (March 20, [1920]). (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - (March 30, [1920]). (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - (April 11, [1920]). (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - (May 12, [1920]). (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - 10 Letters. (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - (July 15, [1920])., 2 Letters. (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - (September 5, [1920]). (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - (September 11, [1920]). (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - (September 26, [1920])., Postscript. (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - (October 10, [1920]). (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - (October 20, [1920]). (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - (December 3, [1920]). (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - (December 11, [1920]). (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - (December 27, [1920])., Postscript. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - 6 Letters. (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - (January 1, 1921). (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - (February 12, [1921]). (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - (March 10, 1921). (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - (March 23, 1921?). (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - (June 25, [1921])., Enclosed in letter from Tsuda Mariko, (June 25, [1921]). (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - (August 26, 1921), Enclosed in letter from Tsuda Mariko, (August 26, [1921]). (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - 5 Letters. (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - (March 19, [1922]). (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - (April 16, [1922]). (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - (October 15, [1922])., Written for Suto Yae by Tsuda Mariko. (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - (November 10, [1922])., Written for Suto Yae by Tsuda Mariko. (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - (November 12, 1922]., Postscript. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Letters., 5 Letters & 1 Postcard. (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - (January 24, [1923]). (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - (February 7, [1923])., Postcard. (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - (February 21, [1923]). (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - (April 4, [1923])., Enclosed in letter from Tsuda Mariko, (April 3, [1923]). (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - (June 5, [1923]). (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - (September 9, [1923])., Written for Suto Yae by Tsuda Mariko. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - 7 Undatable Letters, ca. 1910, 1919-1920. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - 7 Undatable Letters, ca. 1918-1923. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Undatable Letter & Postcard, ca. 1896-1923. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - From Other Family Members
    - Suto Yonekichi., 12 Letters. (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - (January 6, [1897])., Enclosure. (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - [December 21, 1909]., Enclosed in letter from Suto Yae, [December 21, 1909]. (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - (November 20, [1911])., Enclosed in letter from Suto Yae, (November 16, [1911]). (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - (November 27, [1911])., Enclosed in letter from Suto Yae, (November 21, [1911]). (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - (December 5, [1911]). (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - (December 11, [1911]). (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - (February 16, [1915]). (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - (May 5, [1915?]). (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - (May 15, [1915])., Enclosed in letter from Suto Yae, (May 21, [1915]). (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - (July 30, [1915])., Enclosed in letter from Suto Yae, (July 30, [1915]). (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - (August 9, ????). (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - (November 28, ????). (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Tsuda Sen., 7 Letters. (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - (July 19, [1899]). (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - (April 13, [1900]). (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - (May 22, [1905]). (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - (December 20, [1906]). (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - (December 22, [1906]). (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - (December 27, [1906]). (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - (July 28, 1907). (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Tsuda Hatsu., 3 Letters. (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - (December 4, [1898]). (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - [December 4, 1898]. (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - (August 6, ????). (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Uyeno Kotoko., 2 Letters. (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - (December 21, [1909]). (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - (November 24, [1910]). (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Uyeno Eizaburo, 1908-1923.; 6 Letters. (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (December 15, [1908]). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (June 3, 1911). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (August 6, [1911]). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (September 8, 1912). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (June 7, 1915). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (September 18, [1923]). (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Tsuda Umeko, 1897 to 1912.; 25 English Letters. (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (August 7, 1897). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (June 18, 1898). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (August 3, 1898). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (December 10, 1898). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (February 2, 1899). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - [July 28, 1904]. (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (August 12, 1904). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - [October 8, 1904]., Enclosure, Japanese letter, Nannichi Tsunetaro [characters] to Tsuda Umeko, (October 10, 1904). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (July 30, [1906]). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - [1907]. (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (July 20, 1909). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (August 30, 1909). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (November 9, 1909). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (December 8, 1909). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (January 8, [1910]). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (August 14, 1910). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - [January 4, 1911]. (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (June 2, 1911). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (October 24, 1911). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - ([November 3], 1911). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (November 23, 1911). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (December 6, 1911). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (December 30, 1911). (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (November 2, [1912]., Enclosures: newspaper clipping, postcard, and Japanese letter, Mr. & Mrs. Okuma Shigenobu [characters] to Tsuda Umeko, (October 26, [1912]. (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - (December 30, 1912). (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Tsuda Umeko, 1913-1916.; 21 English Letters. (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - [1913?]. (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - (January 14, 1913). (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - (January 20, 1913). (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - (May 10, [1913]). (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - (May 20, 1913). (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - (October 8, 1913)., 3 Enclosures. (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - (October 9, 1913). (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - (November 4, 1913). (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - (November 13, 1913)., A few lines written by Uyeno Mareo [characters], Nakamura Tsuruko [characters], & Suto Yae. (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - (December 13, 1913). (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - (January 10, 1914). (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - [1915]. (Box 19, Folder 7)
        General note
        Page missing.
      - (January 8, 1915). (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - (January 15, 1915). (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - (April 6, 1915). (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - (April 20, 1915). (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - (May 9, 1915). (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - (August 26, 1915). (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - (September 20, [1915]). (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - (April 6, 1916)., Enclosure, Japanese letter from Tsuda Mariko, (April 7, [1916]). (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - (July 24, 1916). (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Tsuda Umeko, 1917-1928.; 11 English Letters. (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - (July 26, 1917). (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - (March 18, 1918). (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - (April 8, 1918). (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - (April 30, 1918)., Enclosure. (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - (May 5, 1918). (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - (July 14, 1918). (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - [October 21, 1918]. (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - (May?, 1919). (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - (May 3, 1919). (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - (October 15, 1928). (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - (October 28, 1928). (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Tsuda Motochika, 1898-1900.; 5 English Letters. (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - (September 27, 1898). (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - (November 23, 1898). (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - (April 16, 1900). (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - (July 24, 1900). (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - (August 27, 1900). (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Tsuda Jiro, 1909-1922.; 6 Letters. (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - (September 27, [1909]). (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - (May 10, [1911]). (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - (June 27, 1911). (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - (March 27, [1915]). (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - ([August] 11, [1922]). (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - (February 11, ????). (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Tsuda Mariko, 1896-1919.; 14 Letters & 2 Postcards. (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - (April 17, ????). (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - (September 8, ????). (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - [September 17. 1907]., Enclosed in Suto Yae's letter, (September 16, [1907]). (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - (February 15, [1911])., Postcard. (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - [July 28, 1911]., Postcard. (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - (January 1, 1912)., Enclosed in Suto Yae's letter, [January 4, 1912]. (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - (December 30, [1912]). (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - (October 4, [1913]). (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - (March 23, [1914?]). (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - (September 9, [1915]). (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - (February 25, [1916]). (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - (November 8, [1916?]). (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - (June 25, [1919]). (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - (July 30, [1919]). (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - (August 14, [1919])., Enclosed in Suto Yae's letter, (August 14, [1919]). (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - [October 11, 1919]., Enclosed in Suto Yae's letter, (October 10, [1919]). (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Tsuda Mariko, 1920-1923.; 16 Letters. (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - (February 2, 1920)., Enclosed in Suto Yae's letter, (February 1, [1920]). (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - (February 12, [1920])., Enclosed in Suto Yae's letter, (February 12, [1920]). (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - (March 31, [1920])., Enclosed in Suto Yae's letter, (March 30, [1920]). (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - (June 6, 1920). (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - (September 11, [1920]). (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - (September 30, [1920?]). (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - (December 8, [1920?]). (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - (June 25, [1921]). (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - [June?, 1921]. (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - (July 13, [1921]). (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - (August 26, [1921])., Enclosure, photograph. (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - (September 20, [1921]). (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - [1921?]. (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - (April 16, [1922])., Enclosed in Suto Yae's letter, (April 16, [1922]). (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - (May 7, [1922]). (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - (April 3, [1923]). (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Weda Jun, 1905-1929.; 8 Letters & 1 Postcard. (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - (March 22, [1905]). (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - (September 2, [1906?]). (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - (November 18, [1906]). (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - (March 27, [1907?]). (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - (August 23, [1907]). (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - (June 27, 1914)., Postcard. (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - (September 9, 1929)., Enclosure, letter from Wada Jun, (September 10, 1929). (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - (October 4, 1929). (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Wada Jun, 1940-1941.; 9 Letters. (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - (May 3, [1940]). (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - (December 25, [1940?]). (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - (March 3, 1941)., Enclosures:Nichibei Shimbun Tokyo branch records & receipts; Letter, Sagitani Seiichi [characters]-to Wada Jun, (February 28, 1941). (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - (June 2, [1941])., Enclosures:Nichibei Shimbun Tokyo branch records & 2 Letters, Sagitani Seiichi to Wada Jun, (May 30, 1941), & Fuji Seiyaku [characters] to Wada Jun, (May 30, 1941). (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - (June 30, 1941)., Enclosures:Nichibei Shimbun Tokyo branch records & letter, Sagitani Seiichi to Wada Jun, (June 30, 1941). (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - (July 7, [1941?]). (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - (July 16, [1941]). (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - (August 5, [1941])., Enclosures:Nichibei Shimbun Tokyo branch records & Letter, Sagitani Seiichi to Wada Jun, (July 31, 1941). (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - (September 2, 1941)., Enclosures: Receipts & Letter, Kobayashi Teiji [characters] to Wada Jun, (August 21, 1941). (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Wada Hanako, 1911-1918., 6 Letters. (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - (May 19, [1911]). (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - (July 25, [1911])., Enclosed in Suto Yae's letter, (July 25, [1911]). (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - (April 10, [1914]). (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - (February 8, [1915])., Enclosed in Suto Yae's letter, (February 8, [1915]). (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - (February 23, [1915?]). (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - (December 13, [1918]). (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Tsuda Fukiko., 4 Letters. (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - [June 3, 1893) &., 3 Undatable letters. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Sakabe Tomiko & Jiro., 6 Letters. (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - (February 2, [1915]). (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - (April 1, 1915). (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - (September 10, [1923]). (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - (September 12, 1923). (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - [1929]. (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - (November 3, [????]). (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Abiko Eiko & Etsuko [characters]., 3 Letters. (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - (April 17 [1913?]). (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - (January 1, 1916). (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - (October 1, [1918]). (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Oi [characters] Family., 8 Letters. (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - (September 9, [1911]). (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - [1911?]. (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - (November 25, [????]). (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - (May 31, [1919]). (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - (August 4, [1921]). (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - (August 11, [1931]). (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - (July 15, [1941]). (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - [1941]. (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - From Abiko Kyutaro., 57 Letters & 1 Postcard. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - 3 Letters. (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - (January 1, 1909). (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - (January 8, [1909]). (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - (January 12, 1909]). (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Letters., 17 Letters & 1 Postcard. (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - (April 28, [1912]). (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - [September 23, 1912]. (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - (September 27, [1912]). (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - (March 13, [1913]). (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - (March 21, [1913]). (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - (March 28, [1913]). (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - (April 4, [1913]). (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - (April 11, [1913]). (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - (April 28, [1913]). (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - (May 9, [1913]). (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - (May 23, [1913])., Enclosure, newspaper clipping. (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - (June 10, [1913]). (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - [June 20, 1913]., Postcard. (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - (June 22, [1913]). (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - (June 30 [1913]). (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - (July 8, [1913]). (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - (July 15, [1913]). (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - (July 18, [1913]). (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - 10 Letters. (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - (July 25, [1913]). (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - (August 4, [1913]). (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - (August 15, [1913]). (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - (August 17, [1913]). (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - (August 25, [1913]). (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - (September 4, [1913]). (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - (April 17, [1914]). (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - (May 29, [1915]). (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - (July 6, [1917])., Enclosure, English letter to Yasuo, (July 6, 1917). (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - (July 15, [1917])., Enclosure, English letter to Yasuo, (July 15, 1917). (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - 9 Letters. (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - (June 1, 1918)., English letter to Yasuo. (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - (August 18, [1918]). (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - (September 6, [1918])., Enclosures, English letter, (May 8, 1918), Consul General of France to Yonako, and English letter, (September 6, 1918), to Yasuo. (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - (September 20, [1918]). (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - (October 13, [1918]). (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - (November 7, [1918]). (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - (December 9, [1918]). (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - (December 20, [1918]). (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - (December 30, [1918]). (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - 7 Letters. (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - (January 22, [1919])., Enclosure, English letter, (January 22, 1919), to Yasuo. (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - [February 23, 1919]. (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - (March 6, [1919])., Enclosure, English letter, [March 6, 1919], to Yasuo. (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - (March 23, [1919]), Enclosures., 3 snapshots. (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - (April 28, [1919])., Enclosure, English letter, (April 28, 1919), to Yasuo. (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - (May 6, [1919]). (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - (November 3, [????]). (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - 11 Letters. (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - (July 19, [1923]). (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - (October 23, [1923]). (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - [October 24, 1923]. (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - (October 28, [1923]). (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - (December 28, [1923]). (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - (January 16, [1924]). (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - [February 18, 1924]., Fragment. (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - [March 2, 1924]. (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - (November 18, [1924]). (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - (November 21, [1924]). (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - (May 17, [1931]. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - From Friends and Associates
    - Ichijo Tsuneko - [characters], Peeresses' School Alumnus & Friend., 5 Letters. (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - [April 21, 1900]. (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - [October 4, 1900]. (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - (June 29, [1910]). (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - (July 11, [1915]). (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - (November 30, [????]). (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Ijichi Mikiko [characters], Peeresses' School Classmate., 6 Letters. (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - ([December] 29, [1906]). (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - [November 12, 1907]. (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - (November 24, [1918]). (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - (December 13, [1918]). (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - (July 4, [????]. (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - (November 17, [1935]). (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Hirabayashi (Ichimura) Fujiko [characters], Peeresses' School Classmate., 6 Letters & 1 Postcard. (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - (February 18, [1909]). (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - (March 22, [1909]). (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - (November 13, [1931]). (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - (December 25, [1935]). (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - (August 13, [1940]). (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - (November 10, 1940)., Postcard. (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - (September 2, [1941]). (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Hoshimo Aiko [characters], Friend & President of Tsuda College, 1908-1940.; 5 Letters. (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - (March 29, [1908]). (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - (April 17, [1910]). (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - (August 18, [????]). (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - [December 10, 1935]., Enclosure, Newspaper clipping. (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - (October 15, 1940). (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Kameno Sada [characters], Watsonville Issei., 3 Letters. (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - (July 31, [1921]). (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - (August 21, [1921]). (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - (July 26, [????]. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Kawai Michiko [characters], Friend & Founder of Keisen Girls' School [characters]., 4 Letters. (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - (June 20, [????]). (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - (December 22, [????]). (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - [1922-1923?]. (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - (July 28, 1934). (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Kozaka Kaneji & Aiko [characters] Cressey Colony Issei Farmer and Wife., 5 Letters. (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - (November 18, 1921). (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - (May 27, [1922?]. (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - (July 1, [1922?]). (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - (July 13, [1922?]). (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - (December 29, [1926]). (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Osawa M. [characters]., 5 Letters. (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - (October 13, [1909])., Enclosed in letter to Abiko Kyutaro, (October 13, [1909]). (Box 22, Folder 8)